BEYZA ERDOĞAN

COMPUTER ENGINEERING

05343548185 kirtan916@gmail.com Kayseri/Talas Github:https://github.com/beyzaerdogn Linkedin:https://www.linkedin.com/in/beyzaerdog

I am a graduate of Erciyes University, Department of Computer Engineering (%30 English). I worked on Python image processing in the Fire Department Drone project. I work part-time as a software developer at Erciyes University Information Technologies Department. I have a TUBITAK project on Artificial Intelligence in Health. It is open to development. I am curious, stable and love to learn.

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (PART TIME)

Asp.net core (Web) developer, Erciyes University, Department of Information **Technology**

August 2023 - June 2024

- Security Camera with Raspberry Pi, Arduino (RE-DE)
- Fingerprint Scanning-Card Scanning System with C (RE-DE)
- Job Tracking System with ASP.NET CORE MVC C#

ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE DEVELOPER

sadektek

September 2023-October 2023(1.5 months)

- Deep learning, ML, Algorithms, Data Science, Python
- Laser Pulse Unmanned Ground Vehicle Project

INTERSHIP

- Raspberry Pi, Nvidia Nano Jetson
- Türk Telecom
- Erciyes University Information Technology Department

PROJECTS

- TEKNOFEST 2023 DRONE -TYPE1 UAV -Python (Data Training, Deep Learning, Artificial Intelligence.)
- RPA Project (Robusta Academy 2 Months Technical RPA Training)
- Movidle Game and Flight Search Java, Java FX, Java Spring Boot (Basic)
- ATM Application Calculator C#

SKILLS/LANGUAGES

- Intermediate Java, Python, C#, OpenGL
- · Adaptability and continuous learning
- Database and SQL
- Data Science, Deep Learning
- Project management
- Team Player
- · Analytical Thinking Persuasion Skill
- Object Oriented Programming
- English B2
- Spanish A1

EDUCATION

TURHAL ŞEKER SCIENCE HIGH SCHOOL BACHELOR OF COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2014/2018 Erciyes University, 2019-2024

REFERENCES

- Dr. TAYYİP ÖZCAN
- Erciyes University/Computer Engineering
- tozcan@erciyes.edu.tr

- Prof. Dr. BİLGE ALBAYRAK ÇEPER
- Erciyes University / Aerospace Engineering
- balbayrak@erciyes.edu.tr

CERTIFICATES

- BTK Academy of Computer Vision
- C# B Level BTK Academy Competency DevOps Solutions (Jenkins) BTK Academy Exam
- Machine Learning MICROPHONE
- B2 English ERCIYES UNIVERSITY
- SHELL/Science Virus ALL AHEAD
- Introduction to Information Technologies
- TURKCELL-Data Science, Machine Learning